I was having a lot of trouble with gas, so the
lever of my bike was
broken, so welcome
to the YouTube channel, your friend Rohit Kushwaha, so
gas, today we have brought a new video for you,
gas, in my last video I had told you that the
lever of my bike was
broken and I had an
accident in which I had no fault, I had told you
what
happened in that, the lever of its handle was bent, so
gas, I took it to the showroom,
they told me that its lever would have to be changed
and gas, I was having a lot of trouble, it started going
up and down, so I had a lot of
trouble, so gas, you will be
shown in the video how I got the lever
changed, how much did it cost,
keep watching the full video, before that, if
you also want to earn two-three rupees daily, then you
can go to the comment section and download the app, in this app you are
getting a lot of money in less coins
and if you download from my link, then
you will get 250 coins on the spot,
which you can immediately transfer into real money  If you
can do the reading, please
go and download this app immediately. The
first 700 people to download this app will
get a guaranteed extra award.
If you use it continuously for three days,
your chances of winning will increase to more than 90%. So
go and
download this app immediately.
You must be seeing that our gas had become crooked
from here and Yemen.
You can see its alignment here. It is
touching here completely. This pipe of ours has also become crooked
here. So now this pipe will have to be
completely changed. We will get this changed as well. So
let's see what our total price of gas is. We will keep
telling you everything in the video. So stay tuned to the video.
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
So gas, you must have seen in the video that you got
our handle changed. After that, the
gauge handle looks quite good. It will look
fine as compared to before. The Australian team,
which was causing a lot of problems earlier, has been
completely changed by me. And this
color assembly, has been completely fixed by me.  Change it
from here and I will
tell you the total of the whole thing, it comes to 1500,
including everything, you got a clutch lever for ₹650,
in this you get the complete clutch and assembly
along with it and gas, this
handle lever for ₹750 you got it completely
and the tax was specially for the labour
charge for them, so gas if you want to
save yourself from this expense then carefully ride the bike
slowly and safe flight and gas
helmet is to show you that you have to
ride the bike slowly, ride it safely, thank you, we will
meet you in the next video, do
not forget to download in the description